A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office of the Vice President, International Program Review Files FA579
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office of the Vice President, International Program Review Files
1979-1982
Rockefeller Archive Center
Carmichael, William D. (William Daniel), 1929-
Puryear, Jeffrey
Ford Foundation
FA579
1.31 Cubic Feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Arranged in 2 series:
1. William D. Carmichael, 1979-1980
2. Alvin Nelson Puryear, 1980-1982
Scope and Contents
Contains reviews of the following programs - Middle East and Africa, International Division, and Developing Country Programs.
- William D. Carmichael, 1979-1980; I
  - Middle East and Africa Review, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Review, 1980 October 8 (Box 1)
  - Middle East and Africa -- New York, 1980 (Box 1)
- Alvin Nelson Puryear, 1980-1982; II
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Bangladesh Office, 1980 October 25 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- New Delhi, 1980 October 27 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Southeast Asia, 1980 October 30 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Office of Latin America and the Caribbean -- Budget Documents and Briefing Materials, 1980 October (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Material re: 1980 Program Review (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Miscellaneous Program Review Information (1/2), 1980 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Miscellaneous Program Review Information (2/2) (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Mexico and Central America Briefing Materials, 1980 October (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Brazil Program Discussions, 1980 October 20 (Box 1)
  - International Division Program Reviews -- Developing Country Programs Program Review -- Meetings Schedule, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Meeting Schedule, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- India, Nepal and Sri Lanka, 1981 November 20 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Bangladesh, 1981 November 21 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Middle East and North Africa, 1981 December 3 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Eastern and Southern Africa, 1981 December 4 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Western and Central Africa, 1982 January 6 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Mexico and Central America, 1981 November 6 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Brazil, 1981 November 7 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Andean Region and the Southern Cone, 1981 November 10 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Southeast Asia, 1981 November 16 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Program Review, 1981 December 18 (Box 1)
  - Developing Country Programs -- Information Papers, 1981 (Box 1)